

CHARLOTTE CHUCA

INTERN

+639351639213



lottechuca.edu@gmail.com



1403 St. Jude Dr. Palmera 3&4 Taytay, Rizal

To gain valuable experience, knowledge and skills in a challenging environment to foster those I have learned from school. In return, I offer my determination to be an asset of your company throughout the duration of my training period.

Experience

Freelance Virtual Assistant (Basic Tasks)

2019-2020

Social Media Manager

2020-2021

Shopify/Amazon Data Entry

2020-2021

Digital Marketing Leads Generation

2022

Education

2017 - 2019

OUR LADY OF FATIMA UNIVERSITY

Senior High School (STEM)

2019 - Present

UNIVERSITY OF RIZAL SYSTEM

Bachelor of Science in Information System

Expertise

- Visual Design
- With creative thinking.
- Knowledge in Microsoft Office Applications.
- Touch-typist at a range of 40 to 50 words per minute at 100% accuracy.
- Teamwork.
- Well- organized.
- Detail oriented.

SEMINARS AND TRAININGS

- Participated in Leadership Training for SSG, SPG, and Adviser
- Virtual Platform Management Using Microsoft
- Virtual Platform Management Using Google Forms
- Laravel PHP Framework Course
- Java Programming
- Virtual Assistance Training Course

Reference

Reuben V. Buencamino

Online Business Manager at ACB Digital Marketing Services **Phone**

09172401996

Rolando Chuca Jr

Axi / Client Due Diligence Team Lead

Phone

+63 9217164960

Karen Cisnero

Virtual Assistant Agency Owner

Gmail

karen@karenremotely.com